(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
はあちゃまっちゃま～！
Haachama-chama~!
はあちゃまっちゃま～！赤井はあとよ！
Haachama-chama~! It's Akai Haato!
みんなも一緒に！
Everyone, join in!
重ねた手は ぎゅっと離さずに
Keep those joined hands tight, don't let go
行くよ 夢見る空へ
Let's go, toward the sky we dream of
イェーイ！
Yeah!
はあちゃまっちゃまー！
Haachama-chama!
窓越しに見上げた とても小さな空
Looking up through the window at the tiny sky
ここで出会えたのは 数えきれない奇跡
Meeting here was a series of countless miracles
繰り返し辿った 煌めきを繋いで
Connecting the sparkles we've retraced over and over
星のような笑顔に満ちた
Filled with smiles like stars
Day by day みんなの声が力になる
Day by day, everyone's voices become my strength
Step by step ここでそれぞれ目指すもの
Step by step, what each of us aims for here
それぞれ描くもの それぞれ願った夢
What each of us draws, the dreams each of us wished for
重ねた手は ぎゅっと離さずに
Keep those joined hands tight, don't let go
一人じゃない 描き出す時めき
I'm not alone, this excitement is starting to unfold
振り向く事なく まっすぐに
Without looking back, straight ahead
行くよ 夢見る空へ
Let's go, toward the sky we dream of
笑いあったことや 突き進む茨道
The times we laughed together, the thorny paths we pushed through
思い出いっぱいなのに あっという間の日々
So many memories, yet the days passed in a flash
上書きじゃなくて 名前つけて保存
Instead of overwriting, I'll 'save as' with a name
どれも全部 大切に生きていける
I can go on living, treasuring every single one
One for all みんなの為が力になる
One for all, doing it for everyone becomes my strength
Oh for all 共に賑やかすぎるくらい
Oh for all, echoing together so vibrantly
笑顔がもっと止まらない 想いは膨らんでいく
Smiles won't stop overflowing, our feelings keep growing
重ねたいま ぎゅっと噛み締めた
Tightly savoring the present we've built together
一人じゃない 描き出す時めき
I'm not alone, this excitement is starting to unfold
風を感じたら まっすぐに
Feeling the wind, heading straight
行くよ 夢見る空へ
Let's go, toward the sky we dream of
憧れて手を伸ばし 掴み取ったその光が
Reaching out in longing, that light I finally grasped
...まただね...
...Already...
憧れに変わる
Changing to yearning
繋げよ
Connecting
うわああああ！
Uwaaaaaa!
うわあああああ！
Uwaaaaaaaa!
重ねた手は ぎゅっと離さずに
Holding the hands we joined tightly without letting go
ひとり ひとり 描き出すときめき
The excitement that each person creates
出会ったすべてに ありがとう
Thank you to everything I've encountered
奇跡 起こし ずっと そばにいるよ
Creating miracles, I'll always be by your side
行こう 夢見る空へ
Let's go, to the dreaming sky
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はあちゃまっちゃまー！
Haachama-chama~!
ワールドワイドの最強アイドル、はあちゃまこと赤井はあとです！
The world-wide strongest idol, Haachama, aka Akai Haato!
ということで、今日はね、最強アイドルになるべく、
So today, in order to become the strongest idol,
3つの試練をやっていこうと思います。
I'm going to take on three trials.
そして、1年何年かぶりの3D配信、
And, a 3D stream after one, or how many years,
みんな今日は来てくれてありがとう！
thank you all for coming today!
最後まで楽しんでってね！
Please enjoy until the end!
実はなんとですね、今の放送、そして今歌っていた『夢見る空へ』、
Actually, during this broadcast, and the song I just sang, 'To the Dreaming Sky',
なんと、まあみんな聞いて驚くと思うんだけど、
well, I think you'll be surprised to hear this, but
電流を流しながら歌っていました！
I was singing while electric current was running through me!
はい、なんとね、もうすでに試練は始まっているっていうね、
Yes, surprisingly, the trial has already begun!
驚きの、あの電流アイドルみたいな感じなんですけれどもね。
It's like I'm some kind of electric current idol.
今年の赤井はあとの異名は、もしや電流アイドルになるのではないかと、
I'm thinking Akai Haato's nickname this year might just become 'Electric Current Idol'.
まあ思ってるんだけど。そんな感じでね、この電流の説明をすると、
About this current, I'm running it at level 5 right now.
あの今レベル5、レベル5で電流を流しています。
自分の歌声と音に合わせて電流の強さが変わっていくという感じで、
The intensity of the current changes according to my voice and the sound.
まあサビになって、だんだんだんだん電流のレベルが変わっていくっていう、
The level gradually changes during the chorus,
そういう仕様になっております。
that's how it's set up.
はい、そしてね、まあはあちゃまはさ、最強アイドルだから
Right, and well, Haachama is the strongest idol, so
レベル5ぐらいの電流でうろたえるわけないでしょ？
there's no way I'd be flustered by level 5 current, right?
まあやっぱり、次の曲も用意しているんだけれども、
As expected, I've prepared the next song, but
次の電流レベルはマックスでいっちゃおうかと思うんだけど、みんな...
I'm thinking of going with the maximum current level for it. Everyone...
え、何？なんかちょっと運営さんから「マックスはやめましょう」みたいな。
Eh, what? The staff are like "Let's not do max".
いやいやいや、はあちゃまならできっすて、みんなどう思う？
No, no, no, if it's Haachama, I can do it! What do you all think?
ねえ、はあちゃま電流マックスいけるよね？
Right? Haachama can handle max current, right?
あ、え、このなんか電流が、あの、中間レベルがマックスの間とって10なのね、レベルが。
Ah, eh, this current... the middle level between [start] and max is 10.
ってことはマックスがレベル20と。
That means max is level 20.
まあね、今回ちょっとね、運営さんもなんかすごい心配してるんで、
Well, since the staff are really worried this time,
レベル、さっきまで5で余裕だったんで、
level 5 was easy,
次はね、レベルを10にして、あ、レベルを...
next I'll set the level to 10... ah, the level...
次はね、さすがに電流は... でも今も喋ってる最中流れてんだよね。
Next, the current is... actually it's running even while I'm talking.
そう、レベル5だから、まあ次はレベル10で、早速歌っていこうと思います、ちょっと。
Yeah, it's level 5, so next I'll sing at level 10.
はい、よくこの企画許したなって、もう僕自身も
I'm surprised they allowed this project.
聞いた話によると、なんかすごいいい健康にいいみたいな、
According to what I've heard, it's actually very good for your health,
なんかそういうさ、よくお腹にさつけるとこうなんか筋肉が活性化されて腹筋ができるよみたいな、
like those things you put on your stomach to activate muscles and get abs.
そういうやつらしいのよ。
That's what it seems to be.
だからね、まあ早速ね、ちょっと、やっていこうと思います。
So, I'm going to get right into it.
なんかバグってるけどね、あの、コメント大丈夫かな？
The comments seem a bit buggy, is it okay?
まあそんな感じでね、次はレベル10でやっていきたいと思います！
So with that, I'll do level 10 next!
電流2021年、はあちゃま初配信、電流アイドルとして頑張っていこうと思います！
2021, Haachama's first stream of the year, I'll do my best as an electric current idol!
電流アップよろしく！フー！
Current up, please! Woo!
そしてね、コメントもスーパーチャットもみんなありがとう！
And thank you for the comments and super chats!
痛、痛くないよ、うん、痛くない。全然痛くないの。
Ow... it doesn't hurt, yeah, it doesn't hurt. It doesn't hurt at all.
あのなんかすごいプルプルプルプル、あの、肩にね、
It's just like, my shoulders are vibrating a lot,
そう、なんか低圧が乗ってるみたいな感じなんだけど。
like there's a low voltage on them.
まあね、ということでね、みんなコメントもスーパーチャットもありがとう！
Anyway, thank you for the comments and super chats!
最後まで盛り上がってってね！電流アイドルはあちゃまでした！
Please keep the excitement going until the end! This was the electric current idol, Haachama!
ではこれから、次の歌をレベル10のあの電流で歌っていこうと思います！
Now, I'm going to sing the next song with level 10 current!
オッケー、行く、行くからね！
Okay, I'm going, I'm really going!
ビリビリの試練
Biribiri Challenge
生まれたてのドキドキ響かせよう
Let's make this fresh-born heartbeat resound
最高な時間　最高な仲間と
In the best of times, with the best of friends
キラメキにのって
Riding on the sparkle
Yeah!
キラメキライダー☆
作詞：辻純更　作曲・編曲：石濱翔 (MONACA)
Kirameki Rider☆
Lyrics: Junko Tsuji | Comp/Arr: Sho Ishihama (MONACA)
全然痛くないよー！
It doesn't hurt at all!
覚えてるかな　最初の歌
I wonder if you remember the first song
私　声が震えていた
My voice was trembling
あの日から続く未来は
The future continuing from that day
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
Is the 'today' I grabbed with everyone
もっともっともっと加速するハート
A heart that accelerates more and more and more
行くよどこまでも準備はOK？
I'll go anywhere, are you ready?
キラめく夢の扉を1, 2, 3 キラメキライダー！
The door to sparkling dreams, 1, 2, 3, Kirameki Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキ響かせよう
Let's make this fresh-born heartbeat resound
最高な時間　最高な仲間と
In the best of times, with the best of friends
ここにいるよ見つけてくれたから
I'm here because you found me
君に会いたくてやって来たんだ　みんなで歌おう
I came here because I wanted to see you, let's all sing together
終わらないメロディ
A never-ending melody
キラメキにのって
Riding on the sparkle
Yeah!
全然痛くないよ！
It doesn't hurt at all!
全然大丈夫だよみんな！
I'm totally fine, everyone!
届いていたかな　私の声
I wonder if my voice reached you
届けたいのは君に笑顔
What I want to deliver is a smile to you
不意なもどかしさに悔しくて
Frustrated by sudden impatience
みんなと泣き笑ったね
We cried and laughed together, didn't we?
ギュッとギュッとギュッとすべて抱きしめて
Hold everything tightly, tightly, tightly
行くよどこまでも準備はOK？
I'll go anywhere, are you ready?
進め希望の道を 1, 2, 3 キラメキライダー！
Advance on the path of hope, 1, 2, 3, Kirameki Rider!
好きが過ごせる糧に奏でたいんだ
I want to play so that 'likes' can be nourishment for living
最高な場所　最高なみんなと
In the best of places, with the best of everyone
ここにいるよ見失うはずがない
I'm here, there's no way I'd lose sight
君の心が幸せに染まるように
So that your heart may be dyed with happiness
重ねていくハーモニー
The harmony we layer
キラメキにのって
Riding on the sparkle
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep singing
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep dancing
はあちゃまといっしょ！
Together with Haachama!
だって楽しすぎて止まらない
Because it's so much fun I can't stop
Zutto Yeah!
Always, yeah!
全然痛くないよー！
It doesn't hurt at all!
はあちゃまみんな！
Haachama, everyone!
#はあちゃま3Dで
With #Haachama3D
つぶやきよろしくね！
Please tweet about it!
よろしくー！ Yeah!
Thank you! Yeah!
楽しいといい出すだけじゃ語れない
It can't be told just by saying it's fun
今も今も悩みはあるけど
Even now, even now there are worries but
ここにいるよ私ここにいるよ
I'm here, I am here
君と同じ世界を見つめて
Looking at the same world as you
キラメキライダー！
Kirameki Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキ響かせよう
Let's make this fresh-born heartbeat resound
最高な時間　最高な仲間と
In the best of times, with the best of friends
ここにいるよ見つけてくれたから
I'm here because you found me
やって来たんだ　みんなで歌おう
I've come here, let's all sing together
終わらないメロディ
A never-ending melody
キラメキにのって
Riding on the sparkle
キラメキまとって
Wearing the sparkle
キラメキまとってるよ！
I'm wearing the sparkle!
ビリビリ来てるよ！
It's tingling!
ありがとうみんな！
Thank you everyone!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はあー！ということで、はあ！
Haa! So, haa!
電流を流しながらの試練でしたー！
That was a trial while being shocked by electricity!
みんな、どうだったー？
How was it, everyone?
ありがとー！
Thank you!
拍手もたくさんありがと！
Thanks for all the applause, too!
なんかで今ね待って、やめてちょっと待って
Wait, hold on, stop, just a second...
このBGMがさ、あの、電流足してきてるんだけど
This BGM is, uh, adding more electricity.
まあね、なんと、はあちゃまが叫んだら電流も反応して
Actually, when Haachama screams, the current reacts...
また叫んだ音と共に電流がまた流れるというね
...and flows again along with the sound of the scream.
はあちゃまが電流が流れた時に叫ぶと
またその電流もまた来るっていうね
When Haachama screams when the current flows,
that current comes back again.
なんという、悪循環みたいな感じになってるんだけど
It's like some kind of vicious cycle.
までもね、これでね、電流と一緒に、ライブすることによってね
But you know, by performing live together with electricity...
今年もね、最強アイドルとして、頑張れるんじゃないかと、思います！
I think I can do my best as the strongest idol this year too!
ありがとー！スーパーチャットもありがと！
Thank you! Thanks for the Super Chats too!
レベル10！ありがと！
Level 10! Thank you!
来年はレベルマックスで挑めるように
So that I can challenge it at Max Level next year,
もっと最強アイドルになれるように頑張るから
I'll do my best to become an even stronger idol,
みんな、応援よろしくお願いします！
so everyone, please support me!
というわけで
And so,
まあね、ビリビリの試練は終わったわけで
well, the electric shock trial is over.
この後ね、なんと実はね、ゲストも呼んでおります！
After this, believe it or not, I've actually invited a guest!
はい、それではね、ま一度ね
Alright, well then,
今回はアイドル衣装もお披露目ということで
since I'm revealing my idol outfit this time,
それに着替えるために、ちょっと、部屋に行こうと思います
I'm going to go to my room to change into it.
ということで、またね、また後でね！
With that, see you later!
ありがと！じゃあね！
Thank you! Bye-bye!
いっせーの！
One, two!
最近流行りのはあちゃまクッキング
Lately, the trendy Haachama Cooking.
見た目はこうでも中身はおいしい
It might look like this, but it tastes good.
最近流行りのはあちゃまクッキング
Lately, the trendy Haachama Cooking.
友達に見せたら友達減る
If you show it to your friends, you'll lose friends.
50はーちゃまの強さが欲しいですか？
Do you want the strength of 50 Haachamas?
はあちゃまクッキング 好きになって
Haachama Cooking, come to like it.
Haachama GRAND 50 栄養ドリンク
Haachama GRAND 50 Nutrition Drink
はあちゃまクッキング 好きになって
Haachama Cooking, come to like it.
今、はーちゃまになることができます！
You can become Haachama now!
はあちゃまクッキング 好きになって
Haachama Cooking, come to like it.
てってってっ てってってっ...
Te-te-te-te-te...
はあちゃまっちゃまー！
Haachamachama!
みんなー！アイドル衣装のはあちゃまっちゃまだよー！
Everyone! It's Haachamachama in her idol outfit!
はあちゃまのアイドル衣装見て、みんなも頭はあちゃまっちゃまになってね！
Watch Haachama's idol outfit and make your heads Haachamachama too!
お着替え完了！よしっ、久しぶりの3D配信！
Changing complete! Alright, a 3D stream after a long time!
なんとね、電流で始まるとは思わなかったんだけどね
I didn't expect to start with electric shocks though.
いやちょっとね、今からね、アイドル衣装...
So, now, the idol outfit...
そして、アイドル衣装といえば、なんて...
And speaking of idol outfits...
なんかよく分かんないこと言おうとしたけど
まあ、撮影会をね、していこうと思います！
I was about to say something weird,
but well, I'm going to have a photo session!
そしてね、ゲストを呼んでいるので、ちょっと呼びたいと思いまーす！
And, I've invited a guest, so I'll call her in!
ココ会長、カモン！
Coco-kaicho, come on!
はい、勝ち込みじゃー！いぇーい！
Alright, it's a raid! Yay!
はあちゃま、アイドル衣装じゃー！かわいいっ！
Haachama, an idol outfit! So cute!
いくよー？いくよいくよ？どっちだよ、こっちだよ
Ready? Ready ready? Which way? This way.
近い近い、あ、それか！
Close, close! Oh, that one!
何だと思ったんだよ
What did you think it was?
ガニ股で何してんですかね、と思って
I was wondering what you're doing with your legs bowed.
ま、ということでね、今日はアイドル衣装を、ココ会長と一緒に、ちょっと撮影していこうと思います！
Well, so today, I'm going to take some photos in the idol outfit with Coco-kaicho!
撮影タイム！
Photo time!
はい撮影タイムでーす、かわいいでーす、いいなーいいなー
Yes, photo time! So cute! Nice, nice!
私も着たい。あれ、というか...
I want to wear it too. Wait, by the way...
あ、でもね、ココ会長は来たんだけど、なんかカメラマンがいなーい、ちょっとね
Coco-kaicho came, but there's no cameraman, huh?
誰かいないかな、カメラマンになってくれる...
Is there anyone who can be the cameraman...?
お呼びします、撮ります撮ります、フー！
Calling her in! I'll take the photos! Whoo!
あ、かなたそー！
Ah, Kanataso!
はい、天音かなた、お待たせ。今日はなんとかなたんをカメラマンとして呼びました！
Yes, Amane Kanata, thanks for waiting.
Today, I've invited Kanatan as the cameraman!
なんかポーズをね、やっぱりアイドルだから、アイドルとして可愛いポーズで、ちょっと写真撮ってもらおうかなと
Since I'm an idol, I'll have her take some photos of me in cute idol poses.
お、どんなポーズ？
Oh, what kind of pose?
でもちょっとびっくりしたんだけど、はあちゃま、あの、何、電気を流してたの？
I was a bit surprised though, Haachama, were you... like, being electrocuted?
そうなのー、そう、はあちゃま電流アイドルだから！
That's right! Yeah, because Haachama is an electric shock idol!
はあちゃまっちゃまー、電流アイドルはあちゃま！
Haachamachama! Electric shock idol Haachama!
ヒェ〜。じゃあね、そんな電流アイドルのはあちゃまと、ここにはね、あの、ちょっと、カメラに寄っていただいて
Whoa. Well then, with electric shock idol Haachama, let's have her get close to the camera...
ちょっと顔をね、アップ、アップで、にゃんにゃんポーズとかどうですかね？
...and do an Up Close Nyan Nyan Pose or something?
にゃんにゃん行くよー！
Here we go, Nyan Nyan!
おー可愛い！にゃんにゃん、おー可愛い。
Oh, cute! Nyan Nyan! Oh, cute.
ちょっと前髪があざとすぎて、あーいいっすねいいっすね
Those bangs are a bit too calculated, ah, nice, nice.
はい、これスクショタイムな、スクショ。みんな撮って、みんな撮って
Yes, it's screenshot time! Everyone, take screenshots!
あ、前髪めっちゃ可愛いじゃん、はあちゃま
Ah, your bangs are super cute, Haachama.
あーいい、前髪あー可愛い
Ah, nice, your bangs are so cute.
いいですね、いいですね、なんかかなたのことだからゴリラポーズとか言うのかと思ったら
Nice, nice. I thought Kanata would ask for a gorilla pose or something, knowing her...
にゃんにゃん可愛くて、本当良かった本当に
I'm really glad the Nyan Nyan was cute.
ゴリラポーズもお願いします、はい、ウホウホウホ、ウホウホウホ、ゴリラ！
Please do a gorilla pose too! Yes! Uho uho uho! Uho uho uho! Gorilla!
はい、握力50ありそうなゴリラでお願いしまーす！
Alright, a gorilla that looks like it has 50kg grip strength, please!
あーいいですね、いいですね、結構本物っぽい
Ah, nice, nice. It looks quite authentic.
アイドルを外し、ゴリラになり果てたな...
She's cast off the idol persona and become a full-on gorilla...
あとですね、はあちゃま
Also, Haachama...
あ、パンツがない、あ、なるほど
Oh, her panties are gone... Oh, I see.
（笑い声）
(Laughter)
今日のパンツ何色かなって確認しようとしたんだけど、あ、カメラ！
I was trying to check what color my panties were today, but ah, the camera!
あ、ハッチャマのパンツが！
Ah, Haachama's panties!
パンツは後で。パンツはまだあるから。後で、後で。
Panties later. There's more panties coming, so later, later.
あの、二つ目はTwitterとかでもね、使えるようななんか動画みたいなのがね、欲しいのよね。
Um, for the second one, I want some kind of video that can be used on Twitter and such.
燃えた時とかさ、限界化した時とかに使えるやつがね、いいなと思うんだけど。
I think something usable for when you're "on fire" or when you've reached your limit would be good.
あ、ちょっと待って。あのね、この正面のカメラに向かってちょっと走って…
Oh, wait. You know, run towards this camera in front of us...
すごい顔で驚いた顔とかで「燃えた！ヤバい！」みたいな。
...with a crazy surprised face, like "I'm on fire! This is bad!"
なるほど、なるほど。
I see, I see.
走ってきてくれ。
Run towards it.
なんかあれ、あのガンギマリ顔ってこと？
Like that... you mean that "tripping" face?
ガンギマリの顔で「うわ、燃えたんだけど！」とか言って走ってきてほしい。
I want you to run here with a tripping face, saying "Whoa, I'm on fire!"
ガンギマリで走ってくる！かなたったーん！
Running with a tripping face! Kanata-tan!
ガンギマ…
Trip...
ガンギマリで。びっくり顔、びっくり顔。
With a tripping face. Surprised face, surprised face.
ガンギマリますか？
Are you gonna "trip"?
Are we "tripping"?
ガンギマリますね！あぁぁぁ！
We're "tripping"! Aaaaah!
あれ？何これ？え？ハートが出てる。
Wait, what's this? Huh? Hearts are coming out.
え？ありがとう。なんかすごく出ちゃってるんですか？
Huh? Thanks. Are they really coming out like that?
ちょっと緊張してる、もしかして？
Are you maybe a little nervous?
してない！ガンギマリだぞ！
I'm not! I'm tripping!
ちょっと、なんか驚き顔、あれ？まだ、まだ流れてる…
Wait, your surprised face... huh? It's still, still flowing...
あ、待って！待って！今さ、ここでも走っててさ、パンツが見えた気がする。
Ah, wait! Wait! I feel like my panties were visible while I was running just now.
今、見えた気が…
I think I saw them just now...
なんでパンツなんですか？妖怪かよ。
Why panties? Are you a monster or something?
妖怪かよ。
You monster.
わかりました。じゃあ、最後にやっぱりパンツタイムが必要ってことで…
Got it. Well then, since we need "panties time" at the end after all...
あの、お二人ともね、後ろを向いてお尻フリフリのセクシーダンスをね、踊ってほしいなと思います。
I'd like you both to turn around and do a sexy butt-wiggling dance.
あ、これは…
Oh, this is...
セクシーダンス。はあちゃまにセクシーってできるんですか？電流アイドルが。
Sexy dance. Can Haachama even do sexy? An "electric shock" idol.
お、でき…お、あら！うわぁー！エロ…エロい、エロい。
Oh, they can... oh, my! Whoa! Sexy... it's sexy, sexy.
いいね、その個々の腰の動き。あ、はあちゃまの腰の動きを真似て。
Nice, those individual hip movements. Ah, copy Haachama's hip movements.
はあちゃまも真似て、真似て。もっと、もっと。
Haachama, you copy too. More, more.
もっと。ちょっとローアングル行けますかね、これね？ローアングルで撮っちゃっていいすかね？
More. Can we get a low angle for this? Is it okay if I take a low angle shot?
運営さんいいすか？これ。ちょっともうちょい下から撮っちゃおうかな？ごめん、撮って。
Staff-san, is this okay? Maybe I'll take it from a bit lower? Sorry, I'm taking it.
エロスですね、これ。見えた…あ、止まって！見て、見て！
This is erotic. It's visible... ah, stop! Look, look!
ちょっと、あ、ダメ。ちょっと一生一生、ちょっとぐらいチラッと。あ！見えた！お腹や！お腹！
Wait, ah, no. A little bit, just a peek. Ah! I saw it! It's the belly! The belly!
これが見たかったんだろう、お前らは！
This is what you guys wanted to see!
最高。ありがとうございます。新年、初の、エロライブ、ありがとうございます。
Awesome. Thank you very much. Thank you for the first erotic live of the New Year.
ありがとう！ありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
という感じで僕のターンこれで終わりかな？ありがとうございます。
And with that, I guess my turn is over? Thank you very much.
かなたありがとう！ありがとうね、はあちゃま。ありがとう！
Kanata, thanks! Thanks, Haachama. Thank you!
本屋で買いましょうね！ありがとう。またね。はあちゃま、すしす！
Let's buy it at the bookstore! Thanks. See ya. Haachama, sushisu!
かんそと、かんそと。かんそとだよ。
Kan-soto, kan-soto. It's kan-soto.
あ、はあちゃまなんでパンツ履いてるのこれ？
Ah, Haachama, why are you wearing panties here?
ハッチーから履いてるんです！
I've been wearing them since I was Hatchi!
パンツじゃな…あ、パンツです。電流アイドルのパンツです。ふざけんなよ。
It's not pan... ah, it is. It's the electric shock idol's panties. Don't mess with me.
この人アイドル…本当にこの先輩アイドルなんすかね？不安になっちゃった。
This person is an idol... is this senior really an idol? I've become worried.
あ、ちょ、ちょ、あれ？待って。何してるんですか？
Ah, wait, wait, huh? Wait. What are you doing?
確認してるのよ、今日のパンツの状況を。
I'm checking the status of today's panties.
スタッフさんが困ってるの、今ね。皆さんに説明しておきますと。
The staff are troubled right now. Let me explain to everyone.
よし。じゃあね。あれ？次もまだまだ二人で呼んでいるんで。
Alright then. Huh? We're still calling two more people.
次は誰が来るかな？
I wonder who's coming next?
誰ですか？
Who is it?
おい、おい、おい、おい！すいちゃんだよ！かわ〜い！
Hey, hey, hey, hey! It's Suichan! So cute!
大丈夫かよ。また今度一緒にやる？
Are you okay? Shall we do it together next time?
イェーイ、イェーイ！
Yes, yes!
なんで？ヤバいね。久しぶりはあちゃま。
Why? That's crazy. Long time no see, Haachama.
久しぶり！星街すいせいです！
Long time no see! It's Hoshimachi Suisei!
すいちゃんこんにちはー！
Suichan, hello!
じゃあ、なんか、えーと…何か指定していいってお話なので。
Well then, um... since I was told I can specify something.
ぜひぜひ！
Please, please!
まずはじゃあ、寝転がってもらってもいいですか？
First, can you please lie down?
おっと？寝転がる。ふん。
Whoa? Lying down. Hmph.
はい。寝転がって、はい、寝転がってください。はい、仰向けになって。
Yes. Lie down, yes, please lie down. Yes, on your back.
はい、で、膝を立ててください。
Yes, and please bend your knees.
で、その膝を会長押さえてもらってもいいですか？はあちゃまの膝を。
And, Kaichou, could you hold down those knees? Haachama's knees.
お！膝を押さえる！
Oh! Hold down the knees!
じゃあはあちゃま、腹筋100回！おら、これを撮れ！
Okay, Haachama, 100 sit-ups! Hey, film this!
１！２！３！４！５！６！
1! 2! 3! 4! 5! 6!
なんでよ！写真撮影じゃないじゃん！うぅぅ…！
Why?! This isn't a photo shoot! Ugh...!
頑張れはあちゃま。皆さんぜひね、この汗の…汗の滴るはあちゃまをたくさん撮ってください。
Good luck, Haachama. Everyone, please take lots of photos of Haachama dripping with sweat.
汗の滴る、びしょびしょのはあちゃまをたくさん撮ってください。
Please take lots of photos of Haachama, all drenched and dripping with sweat.
はあちゃま今びしょびしょですね。
Haachama is soaking wet right now.
あ、いい匂いがしてきました！最高です！塗り撮りします！
Ah, I can smell a nice scent! This is the best! I'll take a painting shot!
まだやらせますよ！
I'll keep making her do it!
もう無理！もう無理！
No more! No more!
はあちゃま、あ、もういいですよ。結構がっつりやってくれましたよ。
Haachama, ah, that's enough. You did it quite intensely.
すごい、はあちゃま。さすが電流アイドル。根性が違うぜ。
Amazing, Haachama. As expected of the electric shock idol. Her guts are on another level.
くっそー…もう電流アイドルでしょ、はあちゃま。いつか絶対やり返してやるからな！
Damn... I'm an electric shock idol, right. Haachama. I'll definitely get you back someday!
いつかね。
Someday, huh.
たくさん腹筋したところで、じゃあ次は
Since you've done enough sit-ups, next...
ブリッジをしてください
Please do a bridge.
うわー！ブリッジ！
Whoa! A bridge!
なんか、去年、あの、運営さんに
So, last year, I asked the staff,
「あれ？ブリッジって禁止になったんですか？」って聞いたら
"Hey, was the bridge pose banned?"
「あ…」みたいな顔されたけど
And they gave me this "Uh..." kind of look.
ブリッジもね、あの、転倒しそうになったところを
With the bridge, you know, even if I'm about to fall over,
まぬが、こう、ね、あの、ちょっとね
I can sort of, you know, dodge it and...
なんかブリッジしちゃうみたいな感じでいけば
If I go into a bridge like this...
ほっ！
Hup!
おおー！すごいすごいすごい！
Whoa! Amazing, amazing!
あ、肩が！
Ah, my shoulder!
ちょ、ちょっと、あの、はあちゃま、あの、危ないです！
Wait, wait, Haachama, that's dangerous!
あぁー！
Aaaah!
禁止にした理由が分かりましたね！
Now I see why they banned it!
皆さん、ブリッジはやめましょう。
Everyone, let's stop with the bridge.
今ね、はあちゃまが、今ね、怒られてるんです、スタッフに。
Haachama is getting scolded by the staff right now.
あの、ちょっと私で、私の可愛さで
So, I'll cover with some of my cuteness.
会長の胸写してください！ここ！
Show the President's chest! Right here!
うわー！
Whoa!
危なかったですね。
That was dangerous.
戻りました。
I'm back.
はあちゃま、ブリッジはやはり、あれだったんですね。
Haachama, the bridge really was no good.
そうですね、危なかったんですね、あやうく。
Yeah, that was a close call. Too dangerous.
おっと、ブリッジ！
Oops, bridge!
おっと、ブリッジ！？
Oops, a bridge!?
何回でもいけますけど。
I can do it as many times as I want.
おっとっと、はあちゃま待って。
Whoa, whoa, Haachama, wait.
全力で今、ブリッジやめろって怒られた。
I just got told to stop the bridge immediately.
やめますけどね。
I'll stop, though.
ブリッジはダメだったなー。じゃあ次は
Bridge was a no-go. So, next...
反復横跳びしてもらおうかな。
How about doing some repetitive side jumps?
反復横跳び？いいよ。
Side jumps? Sure.
100回！はい！
100 times! Go!
1！2！3！4！5！6！7！8！9！10！
1! 2! 3! 4! 5! 6! 7! 8! 9! 10!
11！12！
11! 12!
頑張れ、会長も！
Keep it up, President too!
頑張れ、はあちゃま！
Keep going, Haachama!
いいぞいいぞ！光ってる！輝いてる！
Good, good! You're shining! You're glowing!
はぁ、はぁ...無になってしまいました。
*Panting* I've become a void.
はあちゃま、まだまだ！
Haachama, you've got more in you!
うわぁー！
Waaaaa!
はあちゃま、今日も頑張ってるな。
Haachama is working hard today too.
すいちゃーん！
Sui-chaaaan!
はあちゃまがね、今年こそ最強のアイドルとなると言っておりますから
Haachama said she'll be the strongest idol this year,
体力作りは大事ですよね。
so building up stamina is important.
確かにね！なるほどね。
True! I see.
そうなんですよ。そんな汗の、汗もしたたるはあちゃまをね
Exactly. So I was thinking it'd be nice to get some shots
写真撮影できたらいいなと思いまして、皆さん撮れましたか？
of a sweaty Haachama. Did everyone get them?
これ、完璧ですか？
Is this perfect?
どう、どうなの、これ。いい絵撮れたかな、みんな。
How is it? Did you guys get good pictures?
いい絵撮れたかな、みんな。撮れたかな。ありがとうございます。
Did you get good pictures? I hope so. Thank you.
きっとGIFになってね、Twitter上で流行りますよ。
I'm sure it'll be made into a GIF and trend on Twitter.
GIFはあちゃま反復横跳び！
GIF Haachama side jumps!
うわー！
Whoa!
私のターンそろそろ終わりかな。
I think my turn is almost over.
あぁ、すいちゃんありがとう！
Ah, Sui-chan, thank you!
ありがとう、はあちゃま、また一緒に遊ぼうね。
Thanks, Haachama, let's play together again!
一緒に遊ぼうね。ありがとう、今日来てくれて。
Let's play again! Thanks for coming today.
バイバイ！ありがとう。体力作りも頑張っておくね。ありがとう。
Bye-bye! Thanks. I'll keep working on my stamina! Thanks.
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
反復横跳び、まだやるんですか。
You're still doing side jumps?
まだまだ体力が...あ、でもそうだ。後でちょっとやるために
I've still got energy... Oh, but right. To do it later,
後でダンスするから残しとかないと。
I have to save some because I'll be dancing later.
最後まで持たないっすよ、絶対。
You definitely won't last until the end.
そうだよ、体力残しとかないと。おっと、そしたら最後かな。
Exactly, I need to save energy. Oh, I guess this is the last one.
最後にもう一人。
One last person.
おっ！
Oh!
ヤー！ヤー！ヤー！わためおじさんが来たよ！
Ya-ho! Ya-ho! Watame-ojisan is here!
わためおじさん！わためおじさん！
Watame-ojisan! Watame-ojisan!
あれれ、来ちゃったよ。わためおじさんが来ちゃったよ。
Oh my, I'm here. Watame-ojisan is here.
エッチなポーズさせちゃっていいのかな。
I wonder if I can have you do lewd poses.
え、え、え、どのポーズさせるの？
Wait, what? Which pose are you making us do?
まずは
First...
はあちゃま、右腕ちょっと上げてもらって。脇か？
Haachama, raise your right arm a bit. For an armpit shot?
おっと、いいいねー！
Ooh, nice!
で、ちょっと会長の方、ココちゃんの...あ、ココちゃん動いちゃった。
And now, the President... Oh, Coco-chan moved.
まあココちゃんは、わための代わりに、ちょっと脇ペロとか...
Well, Coco-chan, instead of Watame, how about some armpit licking...
脇ペロ！？バカ言ってるんじゃないよ！
Armpit licking!? Don't say such stupid things!
脇ペロダメ？脇ペロNGなの？
No armpit licking? Is that NG?
NGに決まってるでしょ！何言ってるの！
Of course it's NG! What are you talking about!
はあちゃまは別にいいんだけどね。運営さんが許さないかなと思って。
Haachama's fine with it, but I figured management wouldn't allow it.
あ、あ、もう。わためだったら言ってるけどね。
Oh, honestly. I'm telling you as Watame...
絶対許されない、運営さんがダメだし、YouTubeくんが許さないから。
It's absolutely not allowed. Management says no, and YouTube won't allow it.
YouTube NG！脇ペロまずいよ、そんなプレイはまずいよ！
YouTube NG! Armpit licking is bad, that kind of play is bad!
じゃあ次、次、次。わため今端っこにいるんだけど、これ真ん中に寄せてもらえることって...
Okay, next. I'm at the edge right now, can I be moved to the center...
お、来ましたね。じゃあ、はあちゃまとココちゃんのパイで
Oh, here we go. Now, with Haachama and Coco-chan's breasts...
ちょっと、あの、挟んでもらって。アップで、アップで、あの、挟んでもらって。
...sandwich me! In a close-up! Sandwich me!
うにゅにゅにゅ、やばい、わためがやばい！はあちゃまもっと前！前！
Unyu-nyu... this is bad, Watame is in trouble! Haachama, more in front! More!
さあ、わため、前、前！
Okay, Watame, more in front!
スタッフNGですね。ああ、ダメみたい、スタッフのNG出ました。
That's a staff NG. Ah, looks like it's no good, the staff gave an NG.
取れたか？ほら、名前のとこ、自分に置き換えて使えますよ、これね。
Did you get it? See, you can swap your name in and use it, this one.
何に使うか知らんけど。
I don't know what you'd use it for, though.
ムチムチムチムチ...
Plump, plump, plump, plump...
何に使うって何なんだよ、お前！
What do you mean 'what you'd use it for', you!
生贄にする！生贄にする！
I'll sacrifice it! I'll sacrifice it!
胸枕にしてよ！胸枕にしていいよ！
Make it a breast pillow! You can use it as a breast pillow!
恐ろしい... 恐ろしい...
Terrifying... terrifying...
胸枕にしていいよ！
You can use it as a breast pillow!
あ！おじ先輩っす！おじ先輩っす！
Ah! Uncle Senpai! Uncle Senpai!
おじさんさよなら。またおじさよなら。
Goodbye, Uncle. Goodbye again, Uncle.
幸せ... おじさん...
Happy... Uncle...
でもまだやってもいいってこと？これ。
But it's okay to keep doing it? This.
いいよ！またおじさんにやられたい...
It's okay! I want to be done by Uncle again...
じゃ、一個？じゃ、高速で行こう。
Then, one? Then, let's go at high speed.
じゃ、次にやってほしい...
Then, next I want you to do...
まず、はあちゃまが四つん這いで...
First, Haachama on all fours...
四つん這い！もう菓子だろう！
On all fours! You're already a pro!
顔はカメラの方ね。
Face the camera.
赤ちゃまカメラの方。うん。うん。
Akachama, face the camera. Yeah. Yeah.
あ、いいね。で会長は... お尻をちょっとね... 踏んでもいいんだけど... 足を乗せて...
Ah, nice. And Kaichou... the butt a bit... I could step on it... but putting my leg on...
おい！おい！お前！そんなことできるか！そんなことできるか！そんなことできるか！
Hey! Hey! You! Can you do that?! Can you do that?! Can you do that?!
これは... 特殊な癖に...
This is... a special fetish...
特殊な癖のある人に刺さると思うんだよ。
I think this will hit people with special fetishes.
まずよこんなの！まずまず！
This is bad! Bad, bad!
放送禁止だよ！
It's a broadcast ban!
逆、逆は？逆は？逆は？
Reverse, how about reverse? Reverse? Reverse?
なるほど、こっちが四つん這いな。おい！
I see, I'll be on all fours. Hey!
ほら！ほら！ほら！ほら！ほんとに見れねよ会長のこんな...
Look! Look! Look! Look! I really can't watch Kaichou like this...
あ！やばい！尻尾が！尻尾が！
Ah! Bad! The tail! The tail!
そんな苛められるとこ見れないよ！うりゃ！うりゃ！
I can't watch you getting bullied like that! Take that! Take that!
あーん！いいね！尻尾がなんかあれだけど...
Aaan! Nice! The tail is kind of that, but...
尻尾がなんかあれだけど... やばいやばい...
The tail is kind of that, but... bad bad...
いいい！ああ！離して！離して！離して！尻尾やばいちょっと！
Iiii! Aaa! Let go! Let go! Let go! The tail is bad for a sec!
よし！あ、あぶないあぶない。
Alright! Ah, dangerous dangerous.
一瞬やばかったね。
It was dangerous for a second.
すれすれだったね、やばいね。
It was close, bad isn't it.
いやもうおじさん満足しちゃった。
Man, Uncle is satisfied now.
おじさん帰ってください！
Uncle, please go home!
またおじ満足。ありがとう、またね。またやろうね。ありがとうね。
Uncle satisfied again. Thanks, see you. Let's do it again. Thanks.
ありがとうね。またやろうね。ありがとうね。ありがとうね。
Thanks. Let's do it again. Thanks. Thanks.
バイバイ！ありがとうね！バイバイ！
Bye bye! Thanks! Bye bye!
よし！これでバッチリ写真撮れたんじゃないの？
Alright! Didn't we get perfect pictures with this?
みんなも傑作撮れた？いい感じ？
Did everyone get masterpieces? Feeling good?
みんな大事にスクショ撮ってもらって...
Everyone, please take screenshots and treasure them...
まあね、アイドル衣装に着替えたってことは...
Well, since we've changed into idol outfits...
やっぱりね、やることは一つよね。
...as expected, there's only one thing to do.
は？何ですか？
Huh? What is it?
私たち、Hololive English じゃん！English で！
We're Hololive English, right?! In English!
English!
やっぱりね、English で歌っちゃおうと思います！歌っちゃおう！
As expected, I think we should sing in English! Let's sing!
そしてね、今回のテーマは... え、sexy dance を二人で...
And, the theme this time is... uh, a sexy dance by the two of us...
Coco会長直伝のsexy danceで二人で踊りながら歌いながらやっていきたいと思うので、いくわよ！
We want to do it while singing and dancing the sexy dance taught directly by President Coco, so here we go!
Next change! Change! Let's go!
はあちゃま　はあちゃま
HAACHAMA, HAACHAMA
チャンネル登録してよ
SUBSCRIBE TO THE CHANNEL
いついつ　見るの
WHEN WILL YOU WATCH?
毎秒動画見てね
WATCH EVERY SECOND
正気な狂気のコンテンツ
INSANE CRAZY CONTENT
後ろのはあちゃまだあれ
HAACHAMA IS JUST BEHIND YOU
はあちゃま　はあちゃま
HAACHAMA, HAACHAMA
チャンネル登録してる？
ARE YOU SUBSCRIBED TO MY CHANNEL?
いまいま見てよ
WATCH ME RIGHT NOW
毎秒思い出すのよ
YOU WONT FORGET ME
精神のトリップしたいよね
YOU WANT TO BECOME CRAZY?
後ろのはあちゃまだあれ
iM ALWAYS BEHIND YOU
We took our hands towards the brightest screens
All we wish are shinin' dreams
We make our choice with different voice
Oh yes we know Get set and GO!
Sexy! Sexy!
Sexy なんですか！？
Is it sexy!?
Sexy! Let's go!
Uuuh!
You were the one who set this light of smile
it was a dark and hopeless place
It was your shiny eyes that caught me
Filled with hope, THIS STORY STARTS NOW
Notice the fear inside me bouncing up?
That's when I tune my heart beatdown
I will shine, I will smile, my wish will come true
the first page of my history
Voice telling me to "Give it up"
Delete that word my heads are up
I will never be alone, no, not anymore
We are the shiny, smiley star!
We took our hands towards our brightest dreams
Giving all, we are now a team!
I'll blow your mind! Now take my hand!
Let's show this world our dreamland!
Access through my heart, you will see
No regrets with hottest degree
We make our choice with different voice
Oh yes we know Get set and GO!
Glow to the top of my sky above
My precious shiny, smiley days
It's a light you have never seen before
Sending for you, C'mon and get it!
Do you remember all the love that you gave?
It's all here with me, I saved
Every voice, every word I get from you...
But not enough, I want it more
Your precious smile is like a spell
A magic dust that makes me smile
You'll never see my tears
We defeat despairs cause it's my shiny, smiley life
We took our hands towards our brightest dreams.
wonder story, ready to scream?
Together we can make it free
A never ending story
Everyone's a star in this tale
Filled with love and shine and a smile.
We made our choice with different voice
Oh yes, we know Get set and burst!
When I'm sad, you'll be here
When you're torn, I'll be there
Touch my screen and you will feel my heart here
Whenever you're near
There would be no fear
This beat will dry out every tears
Look at my future, shine and glow
make every world to know
My shiny smile!
We took our hands towards our brightest stage
This is me, in my shiny page
Tear of joy and gold happy days
Just a start that we had just made
Hold my hands to see our "MIRAI"
Please my dreams come true for my life
Let the legend start
step by step a miracle
We took our hands towards our brightest dreams
Giving all we are now a team!
I'll blow your mind! Now take my hand!
Let's show this world our dream come true!
Access through my heart, you will see
No regrets my heart is now free
We make our choices with different voices
Oh yes, we will create our WORLD
ありがとう！
Thank you!
というわけで、ココ会長と二人で、Shiny Smily Storyでしたー！
So that was 'Shiny Smily Story' performed by Coco-kaichou and myself!
あーとはあちゃま、ありがとう！
And Haachama, thank you!
会長、来てくれてありがとう！
Kaichou, thank you for coming!
まったねー！
See ya!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
はい、ということで、本当に最高だったー！ありがとう！
All right, that was truly the best! Thank you!
それじゃあ、残すところあと一曲。
Well then, there's only one song left.
やっぱりね、最後はこの曲で、締めたいと思います。
As expected, I'd like to end with this song.
それじゃあ、次の曲、いくよー！
All right, let's go to the next song!
みんな、ホントにありがとう！最後まで最後まで、楽しんでってね！
Everyone, thank you so much! Please enjoy until the very, very end!
2021年も、よろしくー！
Let's have a great 2021 together!
One, two, three, four! Hi! How are you?
RED HEART
作詞・作曲：KOTONOHOUSE
Lyrics & Composition: KOTONOHOUSE
You, are you calling on my phone?
Baby, tell me what is wrong
Don't you ever let me go
Hi, I am good
I am still looking for blue
Am I good enough for you?
Don't you tell me what's my rule
This is me, are you coming other side?
Just gonna set the height
Don't you think about the lie
You and me
Are you ready butterfly?
Alright, alright, alright
Let's go!
Stronger than it
Stronger than it ever been before
This is who I am
Nothing in the way
Don't ever follow away
You and me, make the bottom line
I give to you
My big red heart
Mama, big red heart
I visualize you
My big red heart
Mama, big red heart
はあちゃまっちゃま～！
Haachamachama~!
今年の一番！
This year's best!
はあちゃまっちゃま～！
Haachamachama~!
Hi, overseas!
Thank you for coming along
All the journey of my own
Don't you ever let me go
Yes, this is me
I am falling bottom down
Could you catch me in your arms?
Don't you ever let me go
I want you to just come on other side
Just gonna set the height
I am falling from the sky
Got to see the butterfly
Alright, alright, alright
みんな、今日は楽しんでくれたかな？
I hope you all had fun today!
みんな、はあちゃまっちゃまになれたー？
Did everyone manage to become Haachamachama?
はあちゃまっちゃまー！
Haachamachama~!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Go! Go! Go! Go!
みんな、声出して！はあちゃまっちゃまー！
Everyone, let me hear your voices! Haachamachama~!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Go! Go! Go! Go!
I'm the only girl
Figure out you for in this whole wide world
Figure out of my book, going on with you
I'm looking for the right one on the road
Run down the way, tell me back to you
This can be only you be my home
Stronger than it ever been before
This is who I am
Nothing in the way
Don't ever follow away
You and me, make the bottom line
I give it to you
My big red heart
Mama, big red heart
I visualize you
My big red heart
Mama, big red heart
Mama red heart
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はあちゃまっちゃまー！
Haachamachama~!
赤井はあと
Haato Channel
Akai Haato
thank you for your kind
Subscribe to my channel
Follow my Twitter @akaihaato
Click the like button
SEE YOU NEXT STREAM